|| LAB-NAME: J Lab

|| TASK // Q 1

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo: [Burner, Coil, Insulator]
|SetInfo: [(p:150000), (v:0.0013), (t:515)] // TODO: set valid v and t
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo (property, value, valid-range):
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "Determine the saturation temperature of H20: (constant pressure)
	Initial pressure is 1.5e2 kPa. Apply the insulation layer and set the insulation slider to 100%. Add/remove heat until you are inside the vapor dome."
	Requirements: [(Region:1:0)]
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK


|Type:  [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo: [Burner, Coil, Insulator]
|SetInfo: 
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo (property, value, valid-range):
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "Determine the saturation temperature of H20: (constant pressure)
	What is the saturation temperature of H20 when P = 150 kPa?"
	Answers: ["~ ?? K", "~ ?? K", "~ ?? K"(c)] // TODO: get correct answers
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo: [Burner, Coil, Insulator]
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo (property, value, valid-range):
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "Determine the saturation temperature of H20: (constant pressure)
	Add/remove heat until T = 343 K (70 C)."
	Requirements: [(Temperature:343:5)]
|EfficiencyInfo:

|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo: 
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "Determine the saturation temperature of H20: (constant pressure)
	In which region are you?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid", "Two-phase", "Superheated Vapor"] // TODO: mark correct answer
|EfficiencyInfo: 


|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo: [Burner, Coil, Insulator]
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo (property, value, valid-range):
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "Determine the saturation temperature of H20: (constant pressure)
	Add/remove heat until T = 423 K (150 C)."
	Requirements: [(Temperature:423:5)]
|EfficiencyInfo:

|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:
|SetInfo: 
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "Determine the saturation temperature of H20: (constant pressure)
	In which region are you?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid", "Two-phase", "Superheated Vapor"]  // TODO: mark correct answer
|EfficiencyInfo: 


|| TASK // Q 2

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo: [Weight, NegativeWeight]
|SetInfo: [(p:150000), (v:0.0013), (t:343)] // TODO: set valid p and v
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo (property, value, valid-range):
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "Determine the saturation pressure of H20: (constant temperature)
	Initial temperature is 343 K. Add/remove pressure until you are inside the vapor dome."
	Requirements: [(Region:1:0)] // TODO: mark correct region
|EfficiencyInfo:

|| TASK


|Type:  [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo: [Weight, NegativeWeight]
|SetInfo: 
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo (property, value, valid-range):
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "Determine the saturation pressure of H20: (constant temperature)
	What is the saturation pressure of H20 when T = 343 K (70 C)?"
	Answers: ["~ ?? kPa", "~ ?? kPa", "~ ?? kPa"(c)] // TODO: get correct answers
|EfficiencyInfo:


|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo: [Weight, NegativeWeight]
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo (property, value, valid-range):
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "Determine the saturation pressure of H20: (constant temperature)
	Now add/remove pressure until P = 101 kPa."
	Requirements: [(Region:1:0)] // TODO: mark correct region
|EfficiencyInfo:

|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:  [Weight, NegativeWeight]
|SetInfo: 
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "Determine the saturation pressure of H20: (constant temperature)
	In which region are you?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid", "Two-phase", "Superheated Vapor"]  // TODO: mark correct answer
|EfficiencyInfo: 

|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo: [Weight, NegativeWeight]
|SetInfo:  [Weight, NegativeWeight]
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo (property, value, valid-range):
|QuizInfo: 
	Question: "Determine the saturation pressure of H20: (constant temperature)
	Add/remove pressure until P = 10 kPa."
	Requirements: [(Region:2:0)] // TODO: mark correct region
|EfficiencyInfo:

|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:  [Weight, NegativeWeight]
|SetInfo: 
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "Determine the saturation pressure of H20: (constant temperature)
	In which region are you?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid", "Two-phase", "Superheated Vapor"]  // TODO: mark correct answer
|EfficiencyInfo: 

|| TASK // Q 3a

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:  [Weight, NegativeWeight, Insulator]
|SetInfo:  [(p:101000), (v:0.1), (t:343)] // TODO: set valid t
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "What kind of process is this? (What remains constant?)
	Initial pressure is 101 kPa, and initial volume is 0.1 m^3/kg. Add insulation layer and set its value to 100%. Add mass until P = 8.8e2 kPa."
	Requirements: [(Pressure:880000:1000)]
|EfficiencyInfo: 


|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:  [Weight, NegativeWeight, Insulator]
|SetInfo: 
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "What kind of process is this? (What remains constant?)
	In which region are you?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid", "Two-phase", "Superheated Vapor"]  // TODO: mark correct answer
|EfficiencyInfo: 

|| TASK

|Type: [word-bank]
|ToolInfo:  [Weight, NegativeWeight, Insulator]
|SetInfo: 
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "What kind of process is this? (What remains constant?)
	What type of thermodynamic path did you use in this process?"
	Answers: ["constant pressure", "constant volume", "constant temperature", "constant entropy"(c), "constant enthalpy"]   // TODO: mark correct answer
|EfficiencyInfo: 


|| TASK // Q 3b

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:  [Weight, NegativeWeight, Insulator]
|SetInfo:
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "What kind of process is this? (What remains constant?)
	Bring the pressure to 101 kPa and temperature to 450 K."
	Requirements: [(Pressure:101000:1000), (Temperature:450:2)]
|EfficiencyInfo: 


|| TASK

|Type: [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:  [Weight, NegativeWeight, Insulator]
|SetInfo: 
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "What kind of process is this? (What remains constant?)
	In which region are you?"
	Answers: ["Subcooled Liquid", "Two-phase", "Superheated Vapor"]  // TODO: mark correct answer
|EfficiencyInfo: 


|| TASK

|Type: [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:  [Weight, NegativeWeight, Insulator]
|SetInfo: 
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "What kind of process is this? (What remains constant?)
	Add insulation layer, set insulation value at 100%. Add mass to top of piston and increase maass until pressure = 8.8e2 kPa."
	Requirements: [(Pressure:880000:1000)]
|EfficiencyInfo: 

|| TASK

|Type: [word-bank]
|ToolInfo:  [Weight, NegativeWeight, Insulator]
|SetInfo: 
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "What kind of process is this? (What remains constant?)
	What type of thermodynamic path did you use in this process?"
	Answers: ["constant pressure", "constant volume", "constant temperature", "constant entropy"(c), "constant enthalpy"]   // TODO: mark correct answer
|EfficiencyInfo: 

|| TASK // Q 4b

|Type:  [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:  [Burner, Coil, Insulator, Stops]
|SetInfo:  [(p:101000), (v:0.1), (t:293)] // TODO: determine correct value for v
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "Combined processes: constant P, constant V
	Initial pressure is 101 kPa, initial temperature is 293 K. Attach the insulation layeer and set insulation to 100%. Set a volume stop to 0.3 m^3/kg. Apply the Bunsen burner until the piston just hits the stop, v = 0.3 m^3/kg."
	Requirements: [(Volume:0.3:0.05)]
|EfficiencyInfo: 


|| TASK

|Type:  [reach-state]
|ToolInfo:  [Burner, Coil, Insulator, Stops]
|SetInfo:  
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "Combined processes: constant P, constant V
	Continue to add heat until P = 200 kPa."
	Requirements: [(Pressure:200000:1000)]
|EfficiencyInfo: 

|| TASK

|Type:  [multiple-choice]
|ToolInfo:  [Burner, Coil, Insulator, Stops]
|SetInfo:  
|LimitInfo:
|TargetInfo:
|QuizInfo:
	Question: "Combined processes: constant P, constant V
	What is the final temperature?"
	Answers: ["~ ?? K", "~ ?? K", "~ ?? K", "~ ?? K"] // TODO: determine correct answers
|EfficiencyInfo: 


|| END



